

# **Ivan Gromov**

# Software Engineering Student

Tampere, Finland +358406278445 · <u>ivan.grcmcv@gmail.com</u>

### ⇔ LinkedIn, GitHub

### **Technical Skills**

JavaScript

React

Node.js

Bootstrap

Java

C++

Git

HTML/CSS

**Android Development** 

#### **Hobbies**

Photography, Travel, Music

### Languages

English — Full proficiency

Finnish — Limited proficiency

Russian — Native proficiency

### **Profile**

Enthusiastic and responsible Software Engineering student with the desire to develop himself and apply the acquired knowledge in practice. An experienced and valuable team player, effectively collaborating with others while being able to work independently. A capable software developer who is attentive to details and adaptable to changing circumstances.

### **Education**

Bachelor's Degree Programme in Software Engineering, Tampere University of Applied Sciences, Tampere

August 2021 - Present

## **Relevant Experience**

Student at Samsung IT School, Saint Petersburg

2018 - 2019

- Had experience with Android development.
- Introduced to UX/UI design.
- Made my own applications for Android.
- Experienced in teamwork on a big project.

### **Projects**

Personal Website — React, Bootstrap.

GitHub link: github.com/gromov-ivan/gromov-ivan.github.io

Full-Stack Web Application, To-Do — React, Node.js, MongoDB, Docker.

GitHub link: github.com/gromov-ivan/todo-app

Web Application, Weather Forecast — JavaScript, HTML, CSS.

GitHub link: github.com/gromov-ivan/weather-app

## **Employment History**

Hotel housekeeper, N-Clean Oy, Tampere

April 2022 - Present

A part-time job where I gained my first working experience and performed my duties responsibly and efficiently.

• Work with clients, adhere to the rules, remain flexible and punctual.